Barbaro Reyes

bfreyesgomez@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/barbaro-reyes Portfolio: https://main.d37ylf5je9ws2.amplifyapp.com GitHub: https://github.com/barbaroreyes

SUMMARY

Highly motivated Software Developer, who has worked on a wide range of JS/React single page applications, Express-Node.js microservices on premise and over AWS services. Driven by a need to learn, improve myself, and the solutions I build.

EXPERIENCE

El Chinchorro Mexican Restaurant

Remote, USA June 2021 – Present

Software Engineer

- Sole developer/contributor on the design, architecture and implementation of the restaurant user
- Implemented features that improves customer experience, usability, code quality and productivity using Test-Driven Development, CI/CD, and Agile estimation and planning to provide reliable working features every two weeks.

faced JS/React application, and cloud native AWS backend services. El Chinchorro Web

Technologies: React, JavaScript, Typescript, AWS Services (CloudFormation, CloudWatch, CLI, IAM, Cognito, S3, DynamoDB, Lambda, AppSync/GraphQL)

General Assembly

San Francisco, California March 2021 – June 2021

Software Engineering Immersive

- Develop app projects in JavaScript/React on front-end, JS/Express on back-end.
- Working through daily feedback, issue resolution, and code reviews on GitHub.
- Daily lectures on web development, micro-servicing, and algorithms and data structure.
- Daily standup meetings to facilitate the sharing of ideas and work progress.

Technologies: React, JavaScript, Express, GraphQL, AWS Services

EDUCATION

General AssemblySan Francisco, CaliforniaSoftware EngineerMarch 2021 – June 2021

ThinkfulSan Francisco, CaliforniaSoftware EngineerDecember 2020 – May 2021

CERTIFICATIONS/AWARDS

• Earned many recognitions for my upstanding work on the design, and implementation of the frontend and back-end of <u>Beers Store</u> project.